Your.
Devout.
Worker bee.
Your.
Sad.
Buddly Gumma in the night.
I am Henrik.
And it is you who are falling asleep.
And that's as it is.
What happens happens
And right now there is nothing we can do about it.
Now we start.
And hello fall asleep.
Surly or happy.
Sorry or completely unstable.
My name is Henrik and if this is strange and.
Compliant.
That's how it is.
Because it is here all over it is the whole pod's thought and idea.
I will talk until you fall asleep.
And i won't stick to anything
Or if I want it.
If so then I will stick to some kind of red thread.
But I will simply talk.
Until the sleep enters or the other
As you are looking for what it is now is when you can use
As they are Henrik to exactly what you want.
Today is a story of cuts.
So I will tell you something and then before you now rush away and.
Roars with Tordön's voice.
That Henrik Ståhl should hold on and mansplain
things for me
So I just want to say that it may well happen that it will be so,
But then that is as it is
and that there is nothing you can do about
As firm as the course of time lies the order of the recording.
It is clear that you can choose another section.
Or another podcast
And you can choose a lot of different things, but you can't change the contents of it
Here at it.
I quite often get desires for themes and.
Substances.
And I am very happy for them often so I get ideas from them and feel that
has been a bit fun to try to get in and when sitting here and talking so can
It pops up then.
Yes, but that's exactly the letter and then it can show up.
But, with that said, we are now starting today's story.
Which is aimed at you, which may be a bit.
Annoyed or angry or sad, or
So that you have some kind of negative
Feeling in the body like.
Bent to handle just like this right now.
Acidity.
The so -called surry.
It is the opposite of love
Ugh what what
Robban Brobergs I became now.
This is about.
A city.
Called Surmunda anyway.
Surmunda was one.
Sooty sour location enclosed.
Under one a thick cloud cover.
The narrow dirty streets.
Old.
Such brutal historic buildings.
Constantly hidden in half -dark.
Because the clouds constantly pulled like a blanket between.
The city's surry and and.
Heaven.
It felt like a constant lid was over surry.
A gray lid.
Do you know something that has a gray lid
That thought of a lot lately.
How many times
How many sighs has there so far occurred in the universe
There must be a real figure.
It is clear that you have to decide what a sigh is.
So you could have fun with it a little to say then that.
Or joking to what you make it a little more fun by saying that o k
The sigh must have been performed by a human
It must have been performed in an indignant state thus not an relief of relief
or one
Exhalation that just became a sigh without it to be one.
Sigh.
Imagine having to be damned every damn day.
Type it excuse the swearing.
So.
O k
How many sighs have been performed by people in an indignant state then.
The last two hundred thousand years
Since you also have to draw a line when we became people on real people.
I mean, I know that
our genus, homo sapiens sapiens,
is
An indication, but really it is a sliding scale.
So the last two hundred thousand years.
How many times has one been sighing
I know there is an exact number, although of course it is all the time
Rising because it sighs around the earth as one there was no tomorrow.
Then it was sigh.
So I.
It's just asking that question a little bit and you are happy to guess qualified,
Says it out loud in the room right now.
How many sighs have so far taken place
But this gray lid
So is not a plastic lid.
Or a lid for the ears
Or a lid on expression possibilities.
Without a cloud cover that lies like a lid over Sunda.
Pale light from street lights.
Who blinks desperately seems to fight to survive.
Where.
Along the windingly greedy streets wandered a
Young woman named rubbing.
And she was very small for the plant.
The lack of sunlight meant that you did not grow up as you should.
She has been very short but had a radiance that signaled
greatness presence.
Determination that made her appear larger than her comrades.
She was dressed in.
Work clothes, durable boots.
A cloth tied in the hair.
So such a bandana
Her face was dirty, but her eyes were clear and filled with one.
Used people to say rare curiosity.
Gibba was.
Yes she was showing in town,
She was a collector, you can say just as Pippi Longstocking had expressed.
Her job was to collect stuff she looks through.
So, this is how this now sounds apocalyptic,
Thus, as it is a disintegration a city.
It's a bit like it feels, but it's not.
This is just a city in a parallel reality
Which happens to be covered by fog.
And there was a certain measure of desperation and vulnerability in town of course
precisely because of the lack of sunlight.
But her job was because there was a certain.
Missing in town, there were some buildings like.
Was abandoned in with regular intervals
And then it was her job to walk around and root there.
So sometimes she finds.
Books.
With invaluable fragments of knowledge,
Much was worn and destroyed.
But some things were to interpret.
And she was obliged to hand in everything she found to the Office.
But sometimes she used to break against the law and take home the books first
and try to read and copy on small pieces of paper it she
found worth.
Assimilating
Before she handed in the books to those who decided.
Then you can meet people who do not know what they are on their way
they may know it, but their
Intention running.
Does not show it up and it is often when you end up in these
The situations when you.
Does it go the way for each other and then you should go aside and then go both in the same direction
And then it gets a little.
Confusion.
Then I always laugh and.
Smiles a little over -eating when such happens
And sometimes I get the same reaction back, but sometimes it is too.
Some people can't handle that.
It is too embarrassing or too annoying.
That then I usually feel offended and sad after one.
Such an interaction.
Clinging just knowing what she was on
And she showed with her whole body and her clear clear look.
It was a determination.
People usually know at a long distance.
Which way she would take in a possible meeting.
She went to the city gate.
A large rusty star port.
Of spare parts.
This is really with a maximum theme now, but it may have happened then.
The guard in the gate raised an eyebrow.
When he saw Dibba,
Well, what are you going to do now he said.
She always went out of town.
She got it because she was gathered.
Her job was, after all, to gather stuff that could be to general good,
But he still thought because he was a slightly older gentleman.
So he thought it was a bit his job
to throw small sour glimpses to this young girl who passed by
What are you going to do now, he said.
Shit you in it, she told him then.
That, there he did not like, of course.
The thing is that she did not think that he threw glimpses at her,
But there was nothing he had reflected on.
He thought she was stubborn,
But he dares not say anything more because she was gathered and the collectors were important for.
For town and for the council.
Then, then she pulled out her compass
one one.
Korean series about any type of apocalyptic world there.
The whole of South Korea has become or the entire Korean Peninsula has become one.
Sand desert after some type of apocalyptic event.
I, I think
Netflix has a craze for South Korean series.
Now and had a few years after the squid game, and.
It's.
Exciting, but now I am starting to think, now I think I'm starting to be able to like the structure.
Now a little gets tired of.
This.
so I.
I have not stuck to this one, but it is very nice environments.
They have this sandy.
That's what I see a little in front of me now, though I said this was not apocalyptic.
But there is something about this.
The cloud that has suddenly ridden slid in then.
And hear a little bit the previous knowledge monopoly surgrown in
A darkness that in the long run and removed all.
All of knowledge.
Gribbe knew people were talking shit about her behind her back.
They call her naive and
Maybe crazy even.
Because always went outside the city gate because most of it
The alleys and platforms inside town.
So there was something that could change everything about didn't know what.
She had
Read and seen traces of it in old books she had found.
A world where there was light from heaven and warmth
Where the sun was shining clear.
And this was a world she was.
Abstract decisions to find some way.
I want up above the clouds.
She mumbled for herself
Outside Surmolen.
Stretched a world of.
Livid.
Hills.
Cool gloomy mowing a no man's land.
There were no animals where there were none.
Only in just the wind that
Threw themselves the silent empty tree protection one that stood everywhere
before you are now rushing away.
So if someone says this was just too depressed for one
Collection's section so I just want to say
Giving it a little time now so I'll find really nice warm shifts in this.
But me man, I have to
Paint a little scraper first.
It has to scrape a little in order for it to feel good later.
She had her compass.
She knew that under her, the story hid.
There was another world she had seen the traces of it in the books.
She was safe.
Not sure of anything formulated.
But sure of their own intuition on his own feeling that something.
It was important to discover here.
It was as if
Humanity sometime as the cloud pulled over the world.
Had left.
The spaces between the cities.
There was nothing there, it was empty.
The world was a gray shadow
On ash gray land between the cities.
or a jump or a switch changed and comes in
On something that is just meant it was a backdrop.
Then you can move in a world that looks like the one you just moved,
But it's empty.
There are no n P C where there are no animals there is no one.
No wind in Grenå branches it as one.
Like a painting.
Yes, I think it is so.
It rarely happens now more, because it is so rare that the games
bugs like that,
But when they do, I usually get happy and I usually feel.
Thus, green is oxidized.
Tube of any kind
With 1 small.
Dry.
Very fragile rubber application that is stuck.
It was a face mask that was stuck in this copper tube.
It was covered.
Green, green oxidation and dirt.
But it was something.
So Gribbe had never seen anything like it before.
But there was something with the very structure of the object and the fact
to get up above the clouds.
A machine from the old time, some time before the cloud.
Came sliding.
And removed all the knowledge from the world.
Glimma felt like she had 12 hearts in her chest.
Like to beat the fastest they could.
One heart at a time.
All, she vibrated and sang.
It was so close now.
She didn't know how or why.
But it was so close now this world as she dreamed of.
Her feet.
Trampled it.
Admittedly for her invisible dust on the ground because.
The air was so filled with fog and smoke.
But the sound of her feet against the dry soil below them.
Create it as a drum in her
And as she steps, a troubled feeling also came
Because she knew
That this could be a trouble for her.
The city council and all the others in town.
Many people were afraid of unknown things.
None of those who lived in.
Is who is the age guy here
It can be a woman or man.
But I think the epithet age -old just sounds good.
Often there is someone in all institutions.
It doesn't have to be the person who has the most.
On paper power,
But it is always de facto the person who has the most influence.
So who is age's guy at your workplace or your school fall asleep
Tag a friend.
She decided to tell the age guy for the age group.
In this case, it was actually one who likes her.
Dorin dub
What would happen then
It felt like she had to own the narrative here
because this would not be running away and get way too big and scattered
to make use of it.
It is a general guide among posture I think
when it
Applies to large potentially overthrowing things attitudes.
Idealism, ideal ideal attitudes ideal,
inventions or new knowledge.
Keep it for yourself for a while because
It's S Entier everything.
When it comes to sensitive things to
You yourself understand what it is you send out before you send it out.
She had found something that might change the whole place
Life forever.
But she then chose in the first position that only
Tell that age guy Orin the door dub.
Which was according to rumor, was as old as goals themselves.
At least he was there in the eyes of Gnabba, because she was after all
No more than the opposite old.
Orin door double always sat at the square
In the middle of town on an old old rocking chair one of those standing at Kålgården.
Google rocking chair Carl Larssongården if you are curious about what it is for the rocking chair,
It's like one.
A rocking chair designed by Karin Larsson, who according to rumor was far too.
Weird and uncertain to make the carpenter dare to live deliver it according to
Her measures of daytime so he came in the darkness in the protection of the night.
And delivered it.
It is very low and today it is very gentful, but it may not be
nineteen hundred seven or something when made.
When you are very nice in any case, he sat in.
Ikea did something similar.
Did you know by the way that Ikea is going
It tells Carl Larsson the farm when I was there on a guided tour with my
Family here a few weeks ago.
Then the guide told us that
Ikea goes once a year and guided show at Karlsgården to get ideas
And spread.
I think that is fantastic.
I mean in a time when everything is still documented there is,
It's just google.
Inventory Carl Larsson The farm, so there is a picture of every object.
It's something that going around on the spot.
But this was nothing like guys knew anything about
And neither does Orin Dorin Dubte.
Orin Dorinda double so I rub.
Her voice was very clear, though she was nervous.
I have found something something that can change everything to everything
Throughout the universe.
She replied in this strange way because it was a dialectal thing.
And Orin Dorin double who didn't think it was strange any such universe
I also do not mean that you have to stand grooming yourself as a teenager.
You may feel that you are past that and that is fine,
But at least it makes it easier to see.
But no one never said to trout trout old man without the
let him be held and he doesn't seem to have suffered from it.
With and orin the door, double be kind and wise and fine and I
Don't talk shit about him here.
He immediately understood the seriousness.
And the importance of holding this
underneath lid, so to speak.
So he said that old men first fell in here, so he slipped into his little house.
And you just followed with open your backpack in there.
We at that table in the shady pixel kitchen
and showed him his mask and that arched tuber.
What do you think it might be, do you think
The same thing I whispered she and the penny Dorin Dubbel's eyes widen
When he saw.
That he thought it was.
He thought so.
It's oxygen mask.
Whispered gibba or how orin the door dub a machine from the old world
If this works.
If you can make it work
rectify him because he would not be hurt that she
took too much freedoms so maybe we can use
this one and the like if we can back track how it is built up
So maybe we could get above this cloud cover and see the sun again.
And.
Orin, Dorin, double nodded his eyes were filled with hope.
I think I can fix it.
We can fix it, he said
It was a father's daughter relationship.
Or Dad Grandpa relationship maybe you should say.
I have read some about these machines, you saw BA.
Apparently this idea contains.
Clean air oxygen
If oxygen is missing at high altitudes or there is some missing some, so it is.
And then you need this to be able to be up there without losing consciousness.
Karin said nothing.
Instead, he looks at Gubba.
His gaze was deep and pervasive and he said,
This can change all the knife, but I want you to know one thing.
I won't be able to climb on any mountain peak and perform those experiments
As required, without it you will be.
Must do it.
I am
An old man and my oxygenation is not what it usually has been.
And I.
She had become really sad if you had said I will send one of my
Heads on and do this.
She wanted to be the one.
Would learn and be the first and see if this worked.
So.
She was very happy that she was selected, so to speak.
And he said and so Orin Dorin Dubte that this is also dangerous.
We have to keep this secret because if it gets wrong
Then we can get a riot on our hands so and then he directly translated from English.
Which he often did without knowing if this was part of the actual aart.
It is also dangerous to climb above the clouds,
Not just by different aviation holdings up there.
No man has been over the clouds for hundreds of years.
And.
There is no one, but no one knows what is up there,
What kind of world is up there.
And who sits in their apartment and dare not go out of it
Because they are afraid to break if they go out.
And the outside world has not been so mild to them, you should say.
But still, they themselves stay captured in that apartment
of the fear of breaking if they go out.
They dare not be from each other not before to the customer.
And they never dare.
Never, never.
Ruck on their routines even the smallest and when they do.
So it feels like they are going to break because it rushes in
light and air in those where
The gaps and cavities they suddenly open up.
We can't continue to live, so she said.
And the penny door double nodded.
She was right.
And of course she knew that.
And you also fall asleep, because I have this very clearly.
It's not like there are any doubts, what needs to be done here
And it's really a boring, a dull story,
So I apologize for that, because that's it.
Especially I think when you.
When reading or hearing or seeing a story that
Leaves mass unanswered.
I prefer it to this.
This type of slightly Anglo -Saxon structures that
As I devote myself to here now
But now I'm in on this, so me and I'm bad at the others
The structures themselves.
But during the days that followed now, Orin Dorinda Gubbe and Gibba worked
Every day on this oxygen mask.
How to do to fill an oxygen stub with oxygen
Gubba studied got access through the orin door double
to 1 lot of old texts found in the secret library
and charts and such as she
In some cases in some cases, it was recognized from the fact that it was herself who had gathered it.
And then she could remember that what she had
She tried to understand these complex mechanisms, and.
The cycle that.
Just were really abstract things.
All nights she was in Orin Dorin, double's own secret workshop
Down in the basement.
Behind a door that was not smoked here, Urban Urban Pursuit.
It was a call to 1 guy named Ur.
Sorry.
It was a call for 1 guy named Urban Pursuit.
Urban prince was really had no reconciliation at all.
Yes, the only thing that distinguished him was that he smoked like a so -called brush binder.
One thus a person whose profession is to bind brushes,
But they apparently smoked frequently.
In there behind were they
And kept on and labeling.
It was difficult, of course, the frustrating work.
More than once she wanted to give up.
But every time she stood there
Was about to throw that tank for fanders.
Is out in the door where Urban Urban Burst.
Support.
So first, she reminded herself of what was at stake here.
So she looked
she went up the stairs through the secret gap.
Smoke does not have urban burst or the heat burst my name is coast.
Yes, at least he.
He was dead for a long time.
Urban was on so there was no one who
No one no one cared about it.
After all, it was like a postum thing he had written after Urban Afrase.
Almost like a little
fun fool one, a little trick,
A small bus.
With Urban's reminder.
She looked up at the clouds then she saw that it.
This is what it is all about.
To come to bring some clarity.
And then she continued to work
And I will not go in now fall asleep on the technical stuff.
The steps required because I do not know how to produce pure oxygen.
I don't know how to fill it oxygen.
Think with Syria and such.
So.
I.
No to say that after 2 weeks
Lots of failure so come.
A moment.
Gubba pressed the button on the small
the tube that arranged plastered away all the voice and stuff from
Where you now shiny copper colored.
Button was blue with red
Text on and on the text stood varnish.
Lack but it was old old language for air.
And to hers.
Fantastic joy so the machine started acidic to 1 small
Small click, a small spin,
A small room in rooms, a small burs and a small screw and.
In the end, she put.
And a little sucking sound from the nozzle and she brought it to her nose
and his mouth and pulled in the first dose of his life of
concentrated oxygen, which went straight into the system and she
cried with happiness.
Cribs she has a voice behind her back
As she turned around, Orin Dorinda double stood there with trembling knees
And a voice shaky of emotions.
You did it.
He had been to the toilet all the time.
Old people often go to the toilet for much longer periods of time.
It may take longer, so to speak.
To get off with the shit
So he had been on the toilet for 2 weeks so he had not been able to help her at all
And he was very proud of her.
They still kept it secret.
There was no time to lose, however, so she started preparing for climbing.
There was a mountain
further afield as they had in mind and thought it,
It has looked and going over the clouds, but no one had been there.
She collected ropes and nails.
She studied old maps and routes,
Trained himself for the physical challenge of climbing up a mountain.
When you have never done it before.
All the time she could feel
These 12 hearts in your chest that just thump you like in stereo.
And a little scared she was also of course because it was without a doubt dangerous.
Maybe even deadly
But, she knew she couldn't back out now.
And then one day
So she felt she was done orin dorin dub
had been to the toilet, so she said,
He just said hello through the door to him.
He mumbled just something in response, because he had extra hard
Delivery in there.
And she went away in secret.
The guard.
Had Orin Dorin Dubbe
fittingly replaced for the day and replaced with 1 old dog
Which was dressed press with the nose on the lever.
As soon as there is a human being.
It was carelessly done.
Because there were hazardous enemies also out there that I have not mentioned.
What I won't mention anymore either.
I will see the sun.
Arrested.
Arms and legs ached.
This was no easy climbing.
In the beginning it was just a little oblique uphill, but eventually it became vertical walls
So she had to climb in a way she had never done before and all the time
so low the clouds as
Thick almost physical obstacles that fought against her progress.
The air became thinner and cooler.
It felt like fire when she breathed in
Each step each.
Every little one.
The bundle centimeters were a challenge.
But she continued.
Now I will make a comparison of myself that does not mean
That I'm gibba here.
For guys are a real hero, but sometimes when I'm in the gym
so I can feel that
My body absolutely does not want to do what I want it to do.
I did dips the other day for example, that's when you man.
Hangs in a position and makes it like bending your arms.
It is a
Triceps and chest exercise or I don't know what body parts are.
That i think it tae
On my forearms the underside of my upper arms simply.
Triceps and then
Yes, what I'm really bad at it and I'm really weak and then my body said, said
You should not do this this should not devote it to,
You are one you are.
When doing such
It feels completely silent and very organic,
But I had done it like this
10 times though I didn't want to
So it was so I was in a completely different place mentally.
Sometimes this is what it takes to get over a mental barrier,
That you just continue for a little while.
I do not mean to force yourself to do things that are not good for one,
But in this case, I knew it was good for me in the long run.
After hours of climbing.
She finally felt
But.
Everything was much brighter.
Now it went fast.
The colors start to run through the clouds, first bleached.
And then ever stronger and then
After what felt like an eternity and a second at the same time, she broke through the clouds.
And chair on the top of the mountain
Above them and they were completely white on the top.
And here she stands now.
Gubba as the first in the whole
In several hundred years no one in Surmulna had seen what she saw now with her eyes on
for several generations.
A clear blue
Quite empty sky stretched out endlessly in all directions.
Goal by cloud on clouds on the end to the horizon.
The sun stood as one.
Relentless.
Guest lamp high above so light and beautiful that it almost hurt.
But it hurt for other reasons as well because she had not seen sunlight whole
its life
So it hurt to be at all in
In Enzo C the sun in the periphery.
She could see
This white country that stretched out under and around her in all directions.
Instead of ash gray and lifeless
hills and formations so they were here
Dazzling white.
And she was constantly using her breathing mask.
And it was also a bit to pull in pure oxygen was like one.
Like explosion for every breath, she cried tears off.
Joy of course, triumph and relief,
But also sadness that.
She was alone up there
That she had no one of this with, she knew that.
What is his name O.
Odin Bodin Doobie.
The old man he could not
Ever climbing up
She spent all the rest of the day above the clouds discovered this new world.
Sat there and felt the cool.
Unreasonable wins on their skin.
She was thinking of surrying her people and on all that they
had missed under the clouds and she knew she had to.
She didn't know how to do it, because they had only an oxygen mask.
Yet, she knew it had to happen.
And then the sun went down.
And threw like one.
Sombrero.
A glowing sombrero.
At the horizon and colored the clouds,
Orange and deep blue and pink.
And then she starts her journey back down to Sunda back
to the city.
And it went very fast.
been to release her.
It was actually like they were trying to hold her.
And then she had to again urge her body
to just do the yard itself,
not keep on feeling so much or wait for something to
feel organs instead properly without driven by the memory of the sun and of
the hope of being able to share this beauty with the people down on the ground
So she pressed.
When she finally returns to town, she went straight into Bysala.
Standed on stage, everyone was there.
I have been
And so
What she said is true and he had some toilet paper under one foot,
But no one cares about it.
And to show everyone that she speaks the truth, she activated
the air purifier and held it forward
And it sounded like that from like the oxygen that flowed out.
Heard throughout the hall.
You could hear a button needle fall.
So it was quiet.
And then they finally went.
The skepticals went ahead and breathe in oxygen to try
And could certify and testify that what she said was true.
But not everyone was willing to believe that it was true
and some were also afraid that they had after all
gotten used to.
It was part of their universe, this gray.
The ignorance many were suspicious and were worried that
This news would disrupt the balance.
But there wasn't much to do.
It was like a kind of pandora's box
here.
It was something that had been opened that could possibly be closed again
so despite resistance and fear
So it was so that most people wanted to see the sun.
The first
Climbing Expedition was already departed the next day
And they had decided on they were 8 people brave pioneers with ribs.
And then they had decided to split on the oxygen mask up there.
And when these people came down from there after seeing
the width of beauty up there so it was like to
This was important.
Influential people should say so they could affect people in their
network and eventually
So there was a huge consensus that they had to do something to get rid of the clouds.
And then the big flutter was invented.
The big flutter the flash was a huge solar spring
which was driven by the hand where the guard and the dog.
They pulled in that lever at the door that had been made about
so that.
The big peel the fan could, like blowing back and forth, and when they did
Then the clouds were shipped away in a single high and the dog and the guard.
They had to lead the remuneration.
Which hurts a lot, but it was worth it because they have been so awkward
If the dog is not awkward so it had to suffer unnecessarily
so there is some kind of shadow
shadow in this story and that is that
The dog had to suffer.
The failures of others.
But the clouds blew away, they disappeared.
In front of them and above them.
Stretched an endless sky full of blue.
Small pussies left by the large gray lid.
Up the ground ran flowers in all colors.
Birds suddenly began to sing their joy what they had been before no one
Enter what they had been.
A mild breeze swept down through surround and tangled around in the father of people
and the sun stood there like a stranger high in the sky
Without hiding off clouds.
The new world had begun.
The new world was here, and you just her people.
For now you can actually say so uniformly it was
felt an oo overturn joy lies joy
over to have overcome all obstacles, and.
That it has reached its goal.
And they cried and laughed and sang and drank each other and danced and smiled.
And now, like the real adventure.
To explore this suddenly
Clearly the world around and the enemies that were out there.
They went up in a small blue little smoke, because they had nothing to hide anymore.
This light was anything but relentless and revealing.
It was a beautiful light
And the blue sky accompanied the light in a wonderful almost.
One hundred percent poetic experience.
And Surmolled became a green city.
And in this new country that old people and her people had received.
And then that work begins and I should not say that it was easy as well.
It was a.
It was a difficult job to build a new future.
After all, it is naive and strange and nice at the same time.
This world as it was a real one from Malmborg World
where everyone drank each other to and danced and smiled
And safeguarded the planet about the humans and animals and plants.
On the same.
And they developed effective methods for agriculture and water management.
They protect nature and preserved.
Preserved things but don't let it stand in the way
for a innovative.
Inventive wealth.
And Gibba became manager and top dogg,